{
    "subject": "Sidney_Luft",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Lynn_Bari",
    "human_readable": "Sidney Luft is married to Lynn Bari.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.986301064491272,
            "question": "Is there a known marriage between Sidney Luft and Lynn Bari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9344751834869385,
            "question": "Name a person married to Lynn Bari."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9130544066429138,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Sidney Luft and Lynn Bari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9094295501708984,
            "question": "Who is married to Lynn Bari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9088464975357056,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Sidney Luft and Lynn Bari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8905110359191895,
            "question": "Is Sidney Luft married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8866668343544006,
            "question": "To whom was Sidney Luft married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8591322898864746,
            "question": "Who are Lynn Bari and Sidney Luft?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.762352705001831,
            "question": "What is the name of Lynn Bari's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3410458564758301,
            "question": "Who is Sydney Luft's wife?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sidney Luft is married to Lynn Bari.",
            "html": "yago_24520_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Lynn Bari's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_24520_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Lynn Bari and Sidney Luft?",
            "html": "yago_24520_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom was Sidney Luft married?",
            "html": "yago_24520_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24520_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24520_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24520_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24520_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24520_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24520_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24520_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24520_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24520_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24520_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Sidney Luft was indeed married to Lynn Bari for eight years, from April 1943 until December 1951."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}